Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Schematics, Circuit Notes, and Layouts
  - MRS
    - Repro module - 1) Drilling chart 2) EQ card pin diagram 3) Main cord pin diagram 2 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 34, Folder 20C)
    - Unlabeled MRS folder 1 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Unlabeled MRS folder 2 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 34, Folder 21B)
  - MTI
    - MTI and Crumar design 1 of 2, 1980-05 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - MTI and Crumar design 2 of 2, 1980-05 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Voicing for MTI string-brass filter, 1980-05 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Maestro
    - SM-001 - Fuzz I specifications, 1975-10 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - SM-003 - Phase I notes and graphs, 1975-10 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      Folder also reads "GG5 original."
    - SM-002 Fuzz II notes and graphs 1 of 2, 1975-11-1976-02 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - SM-002 Fuzz II notes and graphs 2 of 2, 1975-11-1976-02 (Box 94, Folder 1C)
    - SM-004 - Phase II notes and graph - stage phaser measurements 1 of 2, 1975-12-1976-07 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - SM-004 - Phase II notes and graph - stage phaser measurements 2 of 2, 1975-12-1976-07 (Box 94, Folder 1B)
    - SM-006 - Two-band parametric specifications, 1976-04 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - SM-008 - Maestro graphic equalizer - notes and graphs, 1976-05-1977-02 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - SM-009 - Volume wah specifications, 1976-06-1976-08 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Maestro compander, 1977-03 (Box 94, Folder 1A)
  - Max Mathews
    - Max Mathew - Electric violin, 1972-09-1973-06 (Box 93, Folder 22)
      Includes letter to Ornette Coleman.
    - Electric violin, 1973-03 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - David McCornack
    - McCornack prototype drawings 1 of 2, 1991-05-1991-10 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - McCornack prototype drawings 2 of 2, 1991-05-1991-10 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Melodian
    - Melodian prototype, Undated (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Mini-Amp
    - Mini-Amp, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Micromoog
    - Micromoog circuit description, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Micromoog concept sketches, Undated (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Minimoog
    - Alternative Minimoog keyboard circuit, 1973-12 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Mini "D" oscillator circuit description, Undated (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Minitmoog
    - SYN-001 Minitmoog notes and graphs, 1974-05-1976-06 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Mod. to Satellite to make Minitmoog, 1976-01 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - SYN-001 Minitmoog specifications, 1976-01-1976-02 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Monitor amplifier/speaker
    - 60-0344 Monitor amplifier/speaker 1 of 2, 1969-12 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - 60-0344 Monitor amplifier/speaker 2 of 2, 1969-12 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Moogerfoogers
    - Moogerfooger diagrams 1 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Moogerfooger diagrams 2 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Multitouch Sensitive (MTS) Keyboard
    - MTS 1 of 2, 1978-1989 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - MTS 2 of 2, 1978-1989 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - MTS, 1981-1992 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Quotations - Cost informations Eaton instrument, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Eaton U/I system, 1982-1983 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Multitouch Sensitive (MTS) Keyboard, 1982-1992 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - MTS keyboard 1 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - MTS keyboard 2 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - MTS keyboard software file structure and source listing, 1990-11-04 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Ontario Science Center
    - Modular equipment for Ontario Science Center, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - PA
    - AMP-011 - 100 watt PA head, 1977-07 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - PA 300, 1977-07 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Parametric equalizers
    - SM-007 - 3 band parametric - information on production model, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - 2 and 3 stage parametrics, 1976-03 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - MI-76-010 - Parametric equalizer, 1976-09-1977-03 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Polymoog
    - Schematic and component location charts - Polymoog model 203A - preliminary, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 20)
  - Polyphonic oscillator bank
    - 60-0463 - R.A. Moog Engineering polyphonic oscillator bank 1 of 2, 1969-08-1970-01 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - 60-0463 - R.A. Moog Engineering polyphonic oscillator bank 2 of 2, 1969-08-1970-01 (Box 94, Folder 5B)
    - Polyphonic performance unit, 1969-08 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Polyphonic oscillator, 1970-08-10 (Box 94, Folder 5A)
    - Polyphonic oscillator bank drawings and description, 1970-08-10 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      Folder also reads: "DWG 1422, 1424, 1425."
  - Preset synthesizer
    - Preset synthesizer 1 of 2, 1970-01-1971-06 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      Folder also reads: "Board diagrams and layouts for preset synth."
    - Preset synthesizer 2 of 2, 1970-01-1971-06 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Mike Quatro
    - Quatrobox, 1972-07 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Ring modulators
    - 8364 ring modulator, 1969-10 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Ring mod, Undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - David Rothenberg
    - Publications re: Rothenberg, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Rothenberg-Massie correspondence, 1965-06-1966-08 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Rothenberg 1 of 2, 1965-11-1969-03 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Rothenberg 2 of 2, 1965-11-1969-03 (Box 94, Folder 8A)
    - Rothenberg prototype, 1965-11-1966-03 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Power supplies, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - RSL, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Rothenberg - obsolete 1 of 2, 1968-06-1968-10 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Rothenberg - obsolete 2 of 2, 1968-06-1968-10 (Box 94, Folder 8B)
    - Rothenberg oscillator boards, power supplies, rack wiring, mixing boards, console wiring 1 of 2, 1968-06-1973-04 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Rothenberg oscillator boards, power supplies, rack wiring, mixing boards, console wiring 2 of 2, 1968-06-1973-04 (Box 94, Folder 8C)
    - Rothenberg thing, 1968-10 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Rothenberg tone panel, center panel schematics, auxiliary keyboard, miscellaneous master oscillator bank 1 of 2, 1968-11-1969-01 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Rothenberg tone panel, center panel schematics, auxiliary keyboard, miscellaneous master oscillator bank 2 of 2, 1968-11-1969-01 (Box 94, Folder 8D)
    - Rothenberg, Undated (Mapcase-folder 18)
    - Rothenberg PCB layout, Undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Rothenberg summary, Undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Samsung
    - Samsung Omniwave 1 of 2, 1995-02 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Samsung Omniwave 2 of 2, 1995-02 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Satellite
    - Satellite information and service manual 1 of 2, 1972-11-1973-01 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Satellite information and service manual 2 of 2, 1972-11-1973-01 (Mapcase-folder 7)
  - Seawright
    - Seawright - Digital controlled envelope generator, 1968-04 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Seawright flipper board, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Second Voice
    - Second Voice, 1971-09-1978-02 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Eric Siday
    - Siday, 1967-08 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - 700 drum modules for Siday and Museum of Modern Art concert, 1969-08 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Solo 800
    - Solo 800 notes 1 of 2, 1973-03-1973-06 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Solo 800 notes 2 of 2, 1973-03-1973-06 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - Sonic V
    - Sonic V diagrams - obsolete, 1971-05 (Mapcase-folder 9)
  - Supersatellite
    - Notes on Supersatellite, 1973-01 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      Folder also has phone numbers and addresses for Luce and Vank listed on it.
  - Chris Swansen
    - Chris Swansen 1 of 2, 1982-03-1982-04 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Chris Swansen 2 of 2, 1982-03-1982-04 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Syn-Amp
    - AMP-001 400 watt Syn Amp specifications 1 of 2, 1976-03 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - AMP-001 400 watt Syn Amp specifications 2 of 2, 1976-03 (Box 94, Folder 10A)
    - Syn-Amp, 1976-07-1976-10 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - AMP-004 Syn Amp #2 notes and graphs 1 of 2, 1976-10-1977-02 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - AMP-004 Syn Amp #2 notes and graphs 2 of 2, 1976-10-1977-02 (Box 94, Folder 10C)
    - Syn-Amp circuitry, 1976-10 (Mapcase-folder 10)
    - Syn Amp II circuitry 1 of 2, 1976-12 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Syn Amp II circuitry 2 of 2, 1976-12 (Box 94, Folder 10B)
  - Synton SPX 216
    - Synton SPX 216, 1985-01 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - TC Electronic
    - TC Electronic, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - TC Electronic SCF, 2001-2002 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - TC Sustain and Para EQ, Undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Isao Tomita
    - Tomita keyboard circuit, 1975-02-1975-03 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - G.R. Thurmond
    - G.R. Thurmond, 1976-01 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - University of Massachusetts
    - University of Massachusetts system - UMass bid 940302 1 of 2, 1975-09-1976-12 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - University of Massachusetts system - UMass bid 940302 2 of 2, 1975-09-1976-12 (Box 94, Folder 11A)
    - Keyboard 1 of 2, 1975-10 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Keyboard 2 of 2, 1975-10 (Box 94, Folder 11B)
    - UMass, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - UMass 1 of 2, 1976-08-1977-09 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - UMass 2 of 2, 1976-08-1977-09 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - University of Massachusetts - Media Center custom modular synthesizer - newly-developed and special-function panels, 1976-08-1977-06 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - UMass, 1977-01-1977-09 (Mapcase-folder 12)
  - Van Koevering
    - Virtual Piano diagrams and construction, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 16C)
    - Virtual Piano diagrams and construction 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Virtual Piano diagrams and construction 2 of 2, 1995 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Interactive Resources, 1995-03 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Virtual Electronics - Van Koevering piano, 1995-03-1995-08 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Virtual Piano, 1995-05-1995-06 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - (Amp-Mixer card) Virtual Piano project, 1995-06 (Box 91, Folder 16B)
    - VP correspondence - Sara, 1995-06 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - E-Mu datasheets and Preditor documentation, 1995-07 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Virtual Piano datasheets, 1995-08 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Van Koevering Virtual Piano 1 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Van Koevering Virtual Piano 2 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 91, Folder 16A)
  - Vocoder - SUNY Buffalo
    - Vocoder, 1967-03-1969-08 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      Folder also reads: "Scott."
    - Vocoder SUNY Buffalo 1 of 2, 1967-03-1970-04 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Vocoder SUNY Buffalo 2 of 2, 1967-03-1970-04 (Box 91, Folder 18B)
    - Vocoder adjust, 1967-11-1970-07 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Vocoder mfg. SUNY Buffalo, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 18A)
    - Vocoder documentation SUNY Buffalo 1 of 2, 1969-08-1970-08 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Vocoder documentation SUNY Buffalo 2 of 2, 1969-08-1970-08 (Box 91, Folder 18C)
    - 290-003 Narrowband active filter - 7848 SUNY Buffalo, 1970-01 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - 1974 Vocoder proposal - office copy 1 of 2, 1974-01 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - 1974 Vocoder proposal - office copy 2 of 2, 1974-01 (Mapcase-folder 14)
  - Yamaha
    - Yamaha Professional System 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Yamaha Professional System 2 of 2, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 19)
  - Ken Yajima
    - Yajima KB 1 of 2, 1975-09-1976-01 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Yajima KB 2 of 2, 1975-09-1976-01 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - 360 Systems Slavedriver
    - 360 Systems Slavedriver, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - 300 series
    - 300 PA head 1 of 2, 1977-01-1977-04 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - 300 PA head 2 of 2, 1977-01-1977-04 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - 300 (B) PA head, 1977-09 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - 400 series
    - 400 Nova Series 1 of 2, 1990-07-1992-03 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - 400 Nova Series 2 of 2, 1990-07-1992-03 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - 700 series
    - 701 drum synthesizer, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - #701, 1969-08 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - 702 percussion synth, 1973-05 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - 900 series
    - 900 series diagrams and specs 1 of 2, 1965-03-1969-08 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - 900 series diagrams and specs 2 of 2, 1965-03-1969-08 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - 902, 1965-04-1965-09 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - 911, 1966-07 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - 60-0347 901A rework 1 of 2, 1966-07-1970-04 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - 60-0347 901A rework 2 of 2, 1966-07-1970-04 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - 961, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - 960 repair manual, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Sequencer Complement Manual, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - 955-956 ribbon control, 1968-02-1969-01 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - 960 sequencer operation summary 1 of 2, 1968-06 (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - 960 sequencer operation summary 2 of 2, 1968-06 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - 950, 1968-12 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - 962, 1968-12 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - 901, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - 901-901 A and B VC oscillators, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - 921B oscillator frequency schematic diagram, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - 961 interface, 962 sequential switch, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - 962 sequential switch operation summary, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - 950-960 combo electronics cover plate, 1969-01-1969-04 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - 60-0196 rework 901B design, 1969-06 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - VC mixer, 1969-06-1969-08 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - 60-0197 rework 956 design, 1969-11 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - 925, 1973-09 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - In process spec sheets, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - 921A, 921B oscillators, Undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - 1084
    - 1084 mixer-amplifier 1 of 2, 1967-06-1968-11 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - 1084 mixer-amplifier 2 of 2, 1967-06-1968-11 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - 1084 1 of 2, 1967-12-1969-01 (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - 1084 2 of 2, 1967-12-1969-01 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - 1125
    - 1125 sample and hold schematic diagram, 1973-12 (Mapcase-folder 17)
  - 1200
    - 1200 mixer 1 of 2, 1969-01 (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - 1200 mixer 2 of 2, 1969-01 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - 1500
    - 1500 tape recorder notes 1 of 2, 1967-01-1968-07 (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - 1500 tape recorder notes 2 of 2, 1967-01-1968-07 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Theremins
    - Theremin 201 drawings, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Battery operated theremin 1 of 2, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      Model 404
    - Battery operated theremin 2 of 2, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - RCA theremin info, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Theremin front panel, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Transparencies for Troubador control panel.
    - Troubador theremin 1 of 2, 1966-1974 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Troubador theremin 2 of 2, 1966-1974 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Professional theremin info, 1967-08 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Greiner theremin, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Theremin - Series 91 1 of 2, 1983-03-1995-12 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Theremin - Series 91 2 of 2, 1983-03-1995-12 (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Warshaw drawings, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Clara's theremin schematics, 1989-04-1989-05 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Ethervox, 1990-03-1990-06 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous theremin data sketch of u-shaped cab., 1991 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Theremin master bill of materials, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Sandberg theremin, 1993-01 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - MIDI theremin, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, notebooks, and mixed files
    - Notebook, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous circuits 1964 and before 1 of 2, 1955-1964 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous circuits 1964 and before 2 of 2, 1955-1964 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Model 505 notebook, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Notebooks, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      Also contains papers dated 1993 labeled "Gary Guster theremin."
    - Notebooks, 1960-1964 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Notebook, 1965-08-1966-12 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Ghent decoder, 1966-06 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Dronge processor, 1967-10 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous notes/schematics, 1968-2000 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous papers - Peter Nero, Rothenberg, A440, touch sensitive keyboard, Hassel, etc. 1 of 2, 1968-1995 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous papers - Peter Nero, Rothenberg, A440, touch sensitive keyboard, Hassel, etc. 2 of 2, 1968-1995 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Stereo preamp, 1968-03 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Percussion antenna detector, 1969-08 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Second section mini oscillator board, 1970-10 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - VCA temperature stability analysis, 1971-04 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous non-projects, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      Folder also reads: "1. A-440 osc and beat indicator; 2. Ed Kalehoff mic preamp; 3. Don Hall ring mod; 4. Battery-powered mic mixer; 5. Battery-powered mic preamp."
    - Moog matrix tester, 1972-09 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Four pad preset drum, 1972-10 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks, 1973-1976 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Brasstown Banger, 1973-05 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Proposed filter IC project, 1974-06 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Test box and "A" noise weighting network, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Comparison box, 1975-12 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Preamplifier, 1976-11 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Pearl microphone report, 1977-03 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Chamberlin drawings, 1984-05-1985-06 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Direct box, 1992-04 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Butts drawings, 1992-12 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Notes and drawings, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Etherwave Pro theremin 761 4481, 2004-04-2004-05 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Etherwave Pro stand, 2004-05 (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - DIY, Undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Mixer circuitry, Undated (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Unknown project, Undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
      44 key multiplexer, sensor amplifier, autocalibration window calibrator, Wien Bridge oscillator, and other circuit blocks.
    - Variable frequency oscillator, Undated (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Events, 1960-2005
  Includes flyers, invitations, correspondence, and travel arrangements for various conferences, events, and speaking engagements. Includes printed lectures by Moog where applicable. Events include academic conferences, computer/electronic/experimental music conferences, trade shows, university commencements, workshops, and television appearances.
  - Audio Engineering Society (AES) conferences, 1964-2004 (Box 65)
    Includes conference preprints, ephemera, and advertisements, as well as copies of paper reviews by Moog (with their corresponding papers).
  - Awards, 1960-2005 (Box 64)
    Contains documents related to awards given to Moog and related ceremonies.
  - Awards, 1992-2004 (Box 77)
    TEC (1992); Museum of Making Music (undated); MEIEA (1999); NAMM (2004)
    Plaques
  - Awards, 1970-1984 (Box 79)
    1970 Billboard Trendsetter award, AES pin, and Svenska Analog-Sympatisorer medal.
  - New York State Small Businessman of the Year award, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - New York State Small Businessman of the Year nomination binder, 1970 (Box 31)
  - SEAMUS Award, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York honorary degree, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Concerts, 1960-2005 (Box 64)
    Includes concert performances by Moog and/or Moog associates including Chris Swansen, Lydia Kavina, Herb Deutsch, and Gershon Kingsley.
  - Conferences, workshops, and speaking engagements, 1960-2003 (Box 63)
  - Conferences, workshops, and speaking engagements, 2003-2005 (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous appearances, 1976-2003 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Contains 1976 poster for an appearance at a high school and 2003 poster for an appearance in Japan.
- Technical Articles, 1954-1997
  Arranged alphabetically by author. Exceptions include subject-based files which were kept intact (i.e.. "Vocoder files" and "Delta modulation").
  - Technical articles I, 1955-1982 (Box 40)
    Includes academic papers, technical articles, and reference materials collected by Moog.
  - Technical articles II, 1955-1982 (Box 28)
  - EDN circuit blocks, 1975 (Box 39)
    Contains clippings on circuit blocks and engineering from EDN magazine.
  - Moog articles; Electronic Music Review, 1954-1997 (Box 30)
    Includes articles written by Moog, as well as a complete run of the Moog-published Electronic Music Review (1967-1968). Includes 2 reels of Electronic Music Review microfilm. Issues of Contemporary Keyboard Magazine featuring columns by Moog are located in box 42. Speeches delivered by Moog are filed in their corresponding event file in Series V.
    Ithaca, New York
  - Soviet electronics handbook, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Clippings, 1920-2005
  Contains newspaper and magazine clippings of: Moog advertisements, articles about Moog, interviews with/quotes from Moog, and photographs of Moog instruments, collected by both Robert Moog and the Bob Moog Foundation. Also includes articles collected by Moog about electronic music and performers associated with the company, including Wendy Carlos, Lydia Kavina, Clara Rockmore, and Keith Emerson.
  Arranged chronologically by decade.
  - Clippings, 1920-1979 (Box 32)
    Primarily contains clippings from 1960-1979.
  - Clippings, 1970-1999 (Box 54)
    Primarily contains clippings from 1970-1989.
  - Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 35)
  - Clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 39)
  - Clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 55)
  - Clippings, 1927-1979 (Box 73)
  - Clippings, 1970-2005 (Box 74)
    Primarily contains clippings from 1970-1979.
  - Clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 75)
  - Clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 76)
  - Contemporary Keyboard Magazine, 1975-2005 (Box 42)
    Includes several folders of Contemporary Keyboard Magazine (later called Keyboard Magazine), many with bookmarked columns by Bob Moog and Tom Rhea.
  - Van Koevering scrapbook, 1961-1987 (Box 31)
    Scrapbook containing clippings related to David Van Koevering and the Van Koevering family's performances in Curt Emmons Crusaders and other church ensembles.
  - Van Koevering scrapbook materials, 1932-1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Includes photographs and 1932 issue of Radio News with theremin article.
    Loose items removed from Van Koevering scrapbook and foldered separately.
  - Old theremin memorabilia - Loudspeaker issues, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Magazines, 1955-2005
    Publications collected by Moog that do not directly reference Moog or his associates.
    - Magazines, 1955-2004 (Box 56)
      Contains Electronotes (1973-1982); Dr. Dobb's Journal (2003); Sound on Sound (2004); Music Perception (1984-1985); IEEE Spectrum (2003); Keyboard Magazine (2003-2004); Journal of the Acoustical Society of America (1974).
    - Magazines, 1963-2005 (Box 26)
      Contains The New Yorker (1990-1993); The Journal of Music Theory (1963-1969); Wired (2001); Sound on Sound (2002-2003); Attaché (1998); Electronic Musician (2002-2004); Keyboard (2003-2005); Keyboard Magazine (2001); miscellaneous magazines (1995-2005).
- Photographs and Slides (Box 38, 41, 80-89)
  Prints and negatives arranged alphabetically within subject subseries. Slides arranged separately.
  - Bob Moog
    Includes portraits and snapshots where Moog himself is the primary subject.
    - Bob Moog, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Color portraits of Moog, Moog in workshop
    - Bob Moog, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      Moog and associates in his Trumansburg studio
    - Bob Moog outdoors shoot, 1994-10; Moog, Renee; Global Village Photography (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Bob Moog playing synth, Undated (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Bob Moog portraits, 1955-1980 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Bob Moog portraits, 1985-1995 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Bob Moog portraits with Minimoog, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Bob Moog snapshots, 1965-2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      Includes candid and casual photographs of Moog
    - Bob Moog snapshots, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Bob Moog studio headshots, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Bob Moog with Minimoog and Voyager, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Bob Moog with synth, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Bob Moog with touch sensitive device, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Bob Moog, breadboard programming, 1982-02-08 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Early Bob w/ synth, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 22)